<Time>05/30/2022 7:26:01 AM</Time>
<OriginalMessage>
    <Id>980733790177599498</Id>
    <Content>Honestly my opinion on this is that its stupid. I dont know of a car apart from the Civilian command bentley that goes 180, the redeye barely reaches 170, So the speeds are questionable. Mae is a management member and Id like to think she knows better but its possible that some characters run faster than others ( like running sideways up hills ). Even then how does he know its unlimited sprint? If she was using a female ped it could just be how fivem is and she runs faster like i know some default peds do. Overall this is stupid and shouldnt even be considered as he has no proof, nobody has a clip and mae is saying that they were not reading out charges so its a fuckery all around. I dont know what they could have possibly charged her with as Excess speed 25 over is 120 seconds, and Evading is 250. So how they got 1000 is beyone confusing.</Content>
</OriginalMessage>
<AfterMessage>
    <Id>980733790177599498</Id>
    <Content>Honestly my opinion on this is that its stupid. I dont know of a car apart from the Civilian command bentley that goes 180, the redeye barely reaches 170, So the speeds are questionable. Mae is a management member and Id like to think she knows better but its possible that some characters run faster than others ( like running sideways up hills ). Even then how does he know its unlimited sprint? If she was using a female ped it could just be how fivem is and she runs faster like i know some default peds do. Overall this is stupid and shouldnt even be considered as he has no proof, nobody has a clip and mae is saying that they were not reading out charges so its a fuckery all around. I dont know what they could have possibly charged her with as Excess speed 25 over is 120 seconds, and Evading is 250. So how they got 1000 is beyond confusing.</Content>
</AfterMessage>
<Author>
    <Id>703197296560701450</Id>
    <Username>Real Trial Mod Tom</Username>
    <Discriminator>2354</Discriminator>
</Author>
<Channel>
    <Id>917912580012507183</Id>
    <Name>ia-chat</Name>
</Channel>