<Time>06/20/2022 6:29:49 AM</Time>
<OriginalMessage>
    <Id>988329394319790100</Id>
    <Content>Im just going to go over every member that was involved and opinion of this scene from my perspective:

Seth should not get this removed, Command and especially high command are held to a higher standard, we have said it in the past and saying it again now. The punishments served by Jay are 110% correct and they are lucky he was dealing with it as i would have striked them all for 5 days. 
Seth is a high command member and the way it normally goes is high command are serving the punishments. For us to have to convene as a IA team is appaling for him to think he didn't do anything wrong and as a High command member he is lucky to be getting off this easy after this scene.. Guests would be banned for the driving that he was doing today and through how he acted, From my count he offroaded the explorer at the beginning of the pursuit, went too fast and unrealistically driving 5 times before the major 6th crash that ended them up on foot. 

Steven is a newer member and personally i've already apologized because this scene from what i've heard of he had it planned and well done to him for doing that, the scene did not go how he wanted and the fact that he cant have a role-play scene go right because he did it with command members is atrocious. Also looking at the video the claim that Steven was shooting doesn't seem right. From talking to him he said he avoided shooting and that he was in the front passenger seat of the car, skimming over the video I didnt see him shoot whilst in the car ( if im wrong let me know ), otherwise i think it was jayden and hiphop that shot first if i can hear the voices right in the video. 

From that being said. This Internal affairs report from my vote is denied, you may think differently but thats my piece.
Also:
Daniel also should in my opinion have a greater strike as he ended up somehow ending up in a head on after he flipped his vehicle mid air, to my knowledge the only entrance to humaine labs is through that road and he must have off roaded his charger after driving off the bridge with his car flipped, i'm going to reach out to him and question him on that matter. As stated police were at a major fault there through not roleplaying that scene.

The photo that i will attach shows how far Daniel would have to go to get to be on the road.</Content>
</OriginalMessage>
<AfterMessage>
    <Id>988329394319790100</Id>
    <Content>Im just going to go over every member that was involved and opinion of this scene from my perspective:

Seth should not get this removed, Command and especially high command are held to a higher standard, we have said it in the past and saying it again now. The punishments served by Jay are 110% correct and they are lucky he was dealing with it as i would have striked them all for 5 days. 
Seth is a high command member and the way it normally goes is high command are serving the punishments. For us to have to convene as a IA team is appaling for him to think he didn't do anything wrong and as a High command member he is lucky to be getting off as easy as he is after this scene.. Guests would be banned for the driving that he was doing today and through how he acted, From my count he offroaded the explorer at the beginning of the pursuit, went too fast and unrealistically driving 5 times before the major 6th crash that ended them up on foot. 

Steven is a newer member and personally i've already apologized because this scene from what i've heard of he had it planned and well done to him for doing that, the scene did not go how he wanted and the fact that he cant have a role-play scene go right because he did it with command members is atrocious. Also looking at the video the claim that Steven was shooting doesn't seem right. From talking to him he said he avoided shooting and that he was in the front passenger seat of the car, skimming over the video I didnt see him shoot whilst in the car ( if im wrong let me know ), otherwise i think it was jayden and hiphop that shot first if i can hear the voices right in the video. 

From that being said. This Internal affairs report from my vote is denied, you may think differently but thats my piece.
Also:
Daniel also should in my opinion have a greater strike as he ended up somehow ending up in a head on after he flipped his vehicle mid air, to my knowledge the only entrance to humaine labs is through that road and he must have off roaded his charger after driving off the bridge with his car flipped, i'm going to reach out to him and question him on that matter. As stated police were at a major fault there through not roleplaying that scene.

The photo that i will attach shows how far Daniel would have to go to get to be on the road.</Content>
</AfterMessage>
<Author>
    <Id>703197296560701450</Id>
    <Username>Real Trial Mod Tom</Username>
    <Discriminator>2354</Discriminator>
</Author>
<Channel>
    <Id>988298367106969600</Id>
    <Name>Seth IA</Name>
</Channel>